Tapeshwar friends,
once again a very warm welcome to all of you in Chirag Mitra and CSC Center Help channel,
friends, I have brought
very good news for you,
since when have you been waiting that when will the
commission for the UW labor card that you have made, when will the payment come
and where will it come to you, then I will show you its entire
process, the payment has come but as always I would like to make
a small request,
you have not yet subscribed to our channel,
please write on subscribe and
also press the bell icon so that
you will always get notification of our new videos
and if you like the video then please like and share it
because if you like and share then
we get a lot of encouragement
for which we keep bringing updates and if you had any
doubt, you can comment in the comment box
and for taking residence,
you will also get the
link of the video in the description box and comment box, after
watching it, complete the entire process and
wait till it is completed and if you have any
professional question or answer then you
can make the payment from the comment box office, so
come on friends, whatever is on your edit
When the payment has come in deposit, then
open your Digit because I have lost my dipper
and as soon as you
click on the passbook, now the payment of August has come here, the
balance of September is for September-
October and all the
cards made in August in the last one or two days, their payment has been
sent here, so
see here, I have opened the wallet on edit here
and see here, that 5708
backward cards have come for three cards, so here
this labor is also telling by doing commission, so the
payment of all the registrations that you had done in that month has come here and
in the next month, the
payment of September which has gone by one month will also come and I have
made three car drives here, the payment of 3 has
come, similarly
you will get the commission of this registration, so if
you leave your CSC wallet and deposit
half in your Digipay Award wallet, then it will come there,
this comment was being made that we have a
wallet in the Digital Seva Portal, it will come there, if it says so,
friends, absolutely,
none of our payments will come there  It goes into depend
and it is clearly written in the labour, it is
written here that it is labour bail commissioner, so no
device is being
deducted from you, it is absolutely
for you, it is the payment only, so check your payment
and we will meet again in the next video, till then you
seek my permission,
thank you, Jai Hind, Jai Bharat friends.